Guide to the Nate Brown Western Sound Archive Collection ARS.0124
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 1951. Ferencsk, Hungarian State Orchestra, Richter 9/27/61; Walter, Vienna Philharmonic, Schwarzkopf 5/29/60, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1951A. Walter, Vienna Philharmonic, Schwarzkopf. Mahler [Better Source], 1960-05-29; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1955. Rostropovich, Sanders. Massey Hall, Toronto [program enclosed], 1975-02-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1956. Davis, Montreal Symphony, Rostropovich, 1975-02-19; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1960. Walter, Concertgebouw, Schwarzkopf. Mozart, Mahler, Strauss, 1952-06-19; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1962. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Tchaikovsky, Symphonies 4 (9/23/65) and 6 (8/16/69). WCLV Marathon, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1969. Fournier Plays Cello Concerti By CPE Bach, Vivaldi, Boccherini, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1972. Danon, Zagreb Philharmonic, Rostropovich. Britten and Khatchaturian Program, Zagreb Festival, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1973. Rodzinski, New York Philharmonic. CBS, 1944-10-22; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1974. Baroque Concerti and Orchestral Works, BBC, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1975. Giulini, Concertgebouw. Berlioz, Romeo and Juliet. Holland Festival, 1972; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1983. Rother, Berlin Radio, Gieseking. Beethoven, Concerto No.5; Karajan, Berlin Staatsoper. Bruckner, 1944; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1984. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw. Voormolen; Franck; Schumann; Mengelberg Interview 1938, 1940; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1988. Bournemouth Symphony Orchestra. Lutoslawski, Cello Concerto; Michelangeli, Celibidache, ORTF Orchestra TV 12/75, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1991. Louise Grinstead, 1973-03-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1994. Ginette Neveu. Beethoven; Brahms, 1948-1949; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1995. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw. Beethoven, Sixth. Live 1940/Studio, Telefunken, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1996. Vienna Symphony, Michelangeli. Mozart, Schumann. Vienna, 1975; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1997. Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra. Bartok, Haydn, 1976-05-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 1998. Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, 1976-05-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 1998A. Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, 1976-05-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2000. Schmidt-Isserstedt, American Symphony Orchestra. Carnegie Hall, 1969-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2001. Schmidt-Isserstedt, American Symphony Orchestra. Carnegie Hall, 1969-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2002. Martinon/Hague; Dutch Interview ["Tape Defective"], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2003. Martinon/Hague. Mahler Eighth ["Tape Defective"], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2004. Horowitz. Massey Hall, Toronto 2 [program enclosed], 1976-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2005. Horowitz. Massey Hall, Toronto 1, 1976-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2006. Horowitz Interview, CBC, 1975; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2007. Gati, CBC Festival Orchestra, Pratz. Bruch, Ibert, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2009. Rostropovich, Edinburgh Festival. Bach Suites, 1975; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2010. Preview of Nethlands Chamber Orchestra American Tour [Radio Nederland 394.838], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2011. Goldberg, Lupu. Aldeburgh Festival. Mozart, Hindemith, Beethoven [possibly switched reels with 1091], 1973; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 32)
- 2012. Walter, Vienna Philharmonic. Salzburg Festival [CBS-Sony SOCO-110], 1956-07-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2020. Jochum, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1960-02-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2021. Klemperer, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1962-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2022. Klemperer, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1962-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2023. Klemperer, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2024. Klemperer, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2026A. Klemperer, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1962-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2026B. Klemperer, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1962-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2034. Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra. Mozart, Hindemith. Dutch Concert Hall 413-957, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2035. Furtwangler, Hamburg State Orchestra 6/9/47; Knappenbusch, Vienna Philharmonic 6/44, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2038. Horenstein, Birmingham Symphony, 1965-03-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2040. Michelangeli. Steinberg, NY Philharmonic 1/8/66; Zdrakovic, Belgrade Philharmonic 1974, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2042. Villa-Lobos, RTF Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2043. Villa-Lobos, RTF Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2048. Schnabel, Oakland 2, 1966-07-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 18)
- 2049. Schnabel, Oakland 1, 1966-07-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2050. Maroth's K.U. Schnabel Interview. College of Holy Names, Oakland, 1966-07-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2051. Claudio Arrau, Piano. Massey Hall, Toronto 11/77; Benno Moisevitch Interview, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2052. Moisevitch Talks About Schumann [; Arrau?], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2053. Akiyama, Vancouver Symphony, Arrau. CBC 12/24/78; Scherchen Interview, CBC 1964, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2064. Programme Inter Nationes 1978. European Festival in Passau, Concert by Bavarian State Orchestra of Munich, 1976; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2065. Programme Inter Nationes 1979. Lindau-Spring Festival, 1977; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2068. Monteux, BSO [crossed out], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2071. Fiedler, Boston Pops 5/5/45; 7/7/45, 1945; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2072. Fiedler, Boston Pops 7/8/44; 7/15/44, 1944; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2074. Solomon, Piano 10/2/56; Lambert, LPO [HMV C.1348/9]; Beecham, RPO c.1956; Beechams Interviewed by Murrow, TV c.1954, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2077. Gilels Recital, Moscow, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2078. Giulini, LA Philharmonic, Roger Wagner Chorale, 1978-10-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2079. Gilels Recital, Moscow Radio, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2080. Svetlanou, USSR State Academic Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2081. Scherchen, TSO. Mahler 7th, 1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2084. Mehta, NY Philharmonic, Horowitz, 1978-09-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2085. Karajan, Berlin Philharmonic, Rostropovich. Strauss, Don Quixote, 1975; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2088. Szell, Boston Symphony, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2093. Walter, NY Philharmonic, Francescatti. Mendelssohn, Violin Concerto, 1947-03-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2094. Robert Trotter Talks To Bruno Walter, KPFK ["Forward to WBAI After Broadcast"], 1961-06-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2095. Walter, New York Philharmonic 3/13/49; 2/27/49; 12/12/48, 1948-1949; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2096. Bruno Walter Selbsportrait, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2097. A. Michaelis Interview With Walter, WQXR, 1955; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2099. B. Walter re: Mozart w/ Fadiman, 1956; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2102. Monteux, SF Symphony Broadcasts 1949-1951; BSO, Berkshire Music Festival, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2104. Monteux, SF Symphony. Early 1950s. Bach; Franck, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2105. Monteux, SF Symphony, Solomon, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2106. Monteux, SF Symphony. Standard Hour, 1945-01-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2112. Gieseking, Lausanne Chamber Orchestra Mozart, Debussy 1948; Barbirolli, NY Philharmonic. Rachmaninoff 1939, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2143. Barbirolli, Halle Orchestra. Bax, Symphony No.3 [HMV C.7593/8], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2114. Rosbaud, Bavarian Radio Orchestra. Haydn [Mercury MG 10050-B], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2115. Rosbaud, Berlin Philharmonic. Haydn [DGG LPM 8363], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2116. Rosbaud, Bavarian State Radio Orchestra [Mercury MG10038], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2117. Rosbaud, Bavarian Radio Orchestra [Mercury MG 10039], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2120. Michelangeli. Chopin, Sonata Op.35; Beethoven, Sonata Op.2 No.3. Firenze, 1952-02-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2121. Michelangeli. Carnegie Hall, 1966-01-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 19)
- 2123. Stravinsky, Craft, Israel Philharmonic. Israel Festival, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2124. Josef Hofman Plays Concertos of Anton Rubinstein, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2126. Klemperer, Philharmonia. Edinburgh Festival, BBC, 1958; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2127. Walter, NY Philharmonic, Wicks, Beethoven 2/15/53; Walter, NY Philharmonic, Morini. Brahms, early 50s, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2128. Melos Ensemble. Schoenberg BBC Studio Concert, 1961; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2129. Backhaus. Beethoven, Appasionata. Salzburg - BFA, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2131. Tortelier, Newmark. Valentini, Bach, Brahms Program. CBC TS Dub, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2134. Menuhin, Gendron, Britten. Aldeburgh Festival, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2137. Henry Wood Promenade Concert. Sargent, BBC Symphony, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2139. Bruno Walter Interviewed By George Powloff, KUSC, 1958; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2140. Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, Fischer. Mozart, Concerto in D, K.466, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2141. [crossed out, says 'blank'], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2142. Walter on Mahler for BWL-3, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2148. Feuermann Plays Beethoven, Sonata No.3 in A and Variations in E-flat; Reger, Hindemith Sonata, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2149. [Hofmann, Bell Telephone Hour?] Herold-Zampa; Beethoven; Chopin 7/31/44; Oresky; Mendelssohn; Rachmaninoff; Chopin 7/30/45, 1944-1945; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2154. Hofmann, Bell Telephone Hour; Columbia Mike Placement Test CO 26504 2/9/40; Ford Sunday Evening Hour 10/19/41, 1940-1945; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2158. Stravinsky, Swiss Italian Radio Orchestra. Lugano 4/29/54; Michelangeli at Bern 3/17/75, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2159. Michelangeli, Piano. Firenze, 1952-02-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2161. Heger, Berlin Philharmonic, Gieseking. Schumann. Studio, Baden-Baden, 1944; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2162. Keilberth, Kolner Rundfunk Sinfonie, Gieseking. Beethoven, 1953-09-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2164. De Sabata 1, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2164 (2). De Sabata 2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2171. Bohm, Vienna Philharmonic. Mozart; Weber; Brahms. Salzburg Festival, 1979; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2176. Klemperer, Los Angeles Philharmonic, 1938-05-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2188. Milhaud and Kirchner in Conversation at Mills 1/59; Madeleine Milhaud On Living With A Composer 10/31/62, etc.; Portrait of Milhaud, CBC Program 5/30/71, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2193. Tributes to Bruno Walter, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2200. Hofmann Bell Telephone Hours (Piano Portions Only), 1943-1947; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2207. Goldberg, Kraus [Parlophone 78s], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2208. Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra. Dutch Concert Hall, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2209. Scherchen, Toronto Symphony. Massey Hall. Direct Dub From Sub-Master, 1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2210. Horowitz. Massey Hall, Toronto [program enclosed], 1979-11-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 2211. [unidentified, poss. part of Scherchen/Toronto 1964?], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2213. Fried, Berlin Philharmonic. Liszt [Brunswick 90163/4], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2214. Henderson, Boyd Neel String Orchestra, Choir, Taylor, Ferrer [Decca AK 1517/21, EDA-13]; De Luca, Pons [Victor 17233 in M-702]; Talich, Czech Philharmonic, Rostropovich, Richter [Supraphon SUA 10404/5]; NBC Toscanini Victor Test Pressings 1939, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2215. De Waart, SF Symphony. Season Opening Concert, 1980-09-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2216. Tennstedt, Cleveland Orchestra. Bruckner, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2217. Gieseking Recital, Seattle, 1956-04-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
- 2219. Rampal, Lagoya Recital, Severance Hall, 1980-02-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2222. Arrau Recital, Toronto. Beethoven Op.10 No.3, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2224. Klemperer, Concertgebouw, Schwarzkopf 2/6/57 [etc.], 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2233. Kubelik, Chicago Symphony. Bartok, Music For Strings, Percussion and Celesta; Brahms, Symphony No.1 WCLV, 1980; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2240. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw. Mahler, Symphony No.4 in G Major [Turnabout TV 4425], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2242. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Vienna Tour. 6/18/65; 6/17/65, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2243. Russian Music - USSR Records, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2249. WQXR Collector's Corner; Prague 1971 Competition First Prize Winners, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2253. Simmons, Oakland Symphony, Arrau, 1981-02-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2255. Kondrashin, Concertgebouw. Nielsen 11/20/80; Kondrashin, L'Orchestre de la Suisse Romande. Prokofiev; Tennstedt, Concertgebouw 2/23/80, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2256. Schmidt-Isserstedt, Vienna Philharmonic, Ricci. Paganini, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2261. Cleveland Orchestra Airchecks, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2278. Goldberg, Babin Recital, Library of Congress, 1966-02-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2281. Reiner, Chicago Symphony, Lewis, Forrester. Mahler, Das Lied Von der Erde; Varviso, Orchestra de la Suisse Romande. Tchaikovsky, Francesca da Rimini, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2282. Del Mar, LSO. Elgar, Enigma Variations, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2292. Rodzinski, RAI. Mussorgsky, Boris Godunov 5/53; Perosi, Il Natale; Bach-Mahler, Suite No. 2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2293. Klemperer, Bavarian Radio Orchestra. Mendelssohn, Symphony No.3 5/23/69; John Cooper. Bibo, Orchestra of America, WNYC American Music Festival 1967, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2301. Bohm, VPO. Mozart, Symphony No.40. Salzburg Festival, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2304. Knappertsbusch. North German Radio Symphony Orchestra. Hamburg 1/15/62; Berlin Philharmonic. Berlin 9/29/52, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2305. Hindemith, BPO. Hindemith, Symphonic Metamorphosis. Inter Nationes, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2310. Simmons, Oakland Symphony 10/18/79; 11/1/79, 1979; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2313. Kondrashin, Moscow Philharmonic. Mahler; Concertgebouw, 1973-11-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2314. Knappertsbusch, 1953-1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2315. Knappertsbusch, 1961; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2317. Hanson, New York Philharmonic [crossed out, "Tape No Good"], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2323. Glenn Gould, CBC Radio 1951-1956; Toscanini, NBC, Serkin 11/26/44, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2324. Gieseking, 1945-1951; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2329. Walter, New York Philharmonic 12/16/45, 2/20/49; Karajan, New York Philharmonic 11/23/58, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2330. Suisse Romande Orchestra, Rubinstein. Brahms 6/24/70; Chopin 5/8/68, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2331. Bohm, NY Philharmonic. Bruckner, 1971-03-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2332. Heward. Hall Orchestra [HMV C.3319/24; Columbia DX1040; Columbia DX1065]; LPO. Lalo [unissued]; Lyndon Jenkins on Heward 5/29/83, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2335. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw [78 dubs], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2340. LH II Position [unidentified, related to 2341?], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2341. Hindemith, ORTF, Haskil 9/22/57; Fricsay, Koln WDR Orchestra, Haskil 5/30/52 [etc.], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2355. MacMillan, Toronto Symphony, Gould [Earliest Known Live Gould], 1951-12-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2365. Scherchen, Vienna Symphony. Vienna Festival 1951; Toscanini, NBC Symphony, Shaw Chorale 2/18/50, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2366. Alessandro, Oklahoma Symphony. WFAA Orchestras of the Nation, 1948-04-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2373. Gulbenician Festival 1961. Copland, National Radio Symphony Orchestra of Portugal; Krips, Hague Residentie, Fournier; Giulini, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, Berganza 1961; Rosbaud, Concertgebouw 1959; Giulini, Hague Residentie 1959, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
- 2375. Szell, Concertgebouw 1959, 1961; Van Beinum, Concertgebouw, Rubinstein 1959; Dresden State Orchestra, Salzburg Festival 1961, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2378. Furtwangler, Devito. Mendelssohn, Concerto; LAPO, Michelangeli. Franck 1/16/49, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2379. Furtwangler. Vienna 1951; Lucerna 1953. Brahms, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2380. Michelangeli. Haydn, Piano Concerto in D; Furtwangler. Mozart, K.466, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2381. Ormandy, Szigeti. Brahms 1952; Rossi, RAI (Turin), Michelangeli 12/23/55, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2383. Furtwangler, Philharmonia, Menuhin. Bartok; VPO. Schumann 1/25/51; Fischer, BRO 1939, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2385. [illegible] Bach, Cello Suite No.3, 1975; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2386. Prague Quartet. Brahms, Prokofiev, Dvorak, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2387. Rieger, Munich Philharmonic, Arrau, Brahms 1, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2387 (2). Prague Quartet 2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2388. Prague Quartet 3, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2391. Ginsburg, Radio Moscow Symphony, Vedernikov. Prokofiev, Concerto for Left-Handed Piano No. 4, Op.55, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2392. Kabalevsky, Leningrad State Philharmonic. Kabalevsky, IV. Radio Moskva, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2393. Dolukhanova. Prokofiev, Songs, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2394. Ogden. Busoni. BBC Studio Concert #10, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2396. Rosbaud, RAI (Rome). Castiglioni, Hindemith, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2397. Furtwangler, Berlin Philharmonic. Wagner, Tristan 10/2/47; Beethoven, Symphony No.6 in F Major 5/23/54, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2399. Melos Ensemble. Poulenc. Aldeburgh Festival, 1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2400. D'Archi, Trio Italiano. Rolla, Beethoven, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2400. Bertini, Israel Radio Symphony, Rostropoviches, Stern, Vishnevskaya 1978; Beecham one man show excerpt, BBC 1979; Beecham, National Anthem, Edinburgh Festival 1950; Ben-Haim, Shostakovich. Israeli Radio, BBC [also says 2190], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2402. Landowska. Handel Suite 1949 [from wire]; other broadcast performances, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2403. Backhaus. Beethoven, Op.111. Salzburg, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2404. Backhaus. Haydn, No.52 in E-flat. Salzburg, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2405. Mahler Recalled (Shorter Version), 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2408. Levine, NY Philharmonic. Mahler, Symphony No.1, 1976-10-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2409. Kunzel, Cleveland Orchestra. Star Wars; Rocky; Send in the Clowns; Girl Crazy, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2410. Fiedler, Boston Pops; Willson, Cleveland Orchestra. Old-Fashioned Band Concert, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2411. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Mozart 1/30/69; Tennstedt. Stravinsky, Orff 7/14/78, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2413. Shaw, Leinsdorf, Szell, Tennstedt, Cleveland Orchestra. Milhaud, Rossini, Hanson, Dvorak, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2421. World Music Festivals. Bergen Festival; Festival of the Two Worlds, Spoleto, 1961; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2422. World Music Festivals. Maggio Musciale Fiorentino; Bergen Festival, 1961; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2426. Scherchen, Philadelphia Orchestra. Haydn, Mahler. Scherchen's American Debut, Off Master Tape, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2427. Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic. Williams 1949; Bloch, Portland Symphony 2/21/49 with discussion and rehearsal, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2428. Rose, Shumsky. Beethoven, Cello Sonata No.3 Op.69; Piano Trio, Op.70. Stratford Festival 8/7/60; Aneerl, Toronto Symphony. Beethoven, Piano Concerto No.5. CBCTV 12/70, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2432. Mitropoulos, WDR Symphony Orchestra of Cologne. Strauss, 1959-09-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2442. Busch, NY Philharmonic [crossed out], 1942-02-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2442A. 2-Track Mozart and Brahms From 2442/3, Pitched, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 22)
- 2443. Busch, NY Philharmonic [crossed out], 1942-02-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2444. Busch. LA Philharmonic. 3/7/46; NY Philharmonic 2/8/42, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2458. Concertgebouw. Hindemith 1/15/49 [Radio Nederland 135-631]; Rosbaud, Holland Festival 6/28/62 [ Radio Nederland 467.929], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2477. Ansermet, L'Orchestra de la Suisse Romande. Debussy. Rehearsal. Radio Geneva 11/11/58; De Sabata, Pittsburgh Symphony. Strauss Excerpt 11/1949; Walter, Vienna State Opera Chorus and Vienna Philharmonic. Verdi, Aida 8/26/37; Black, NBC Ensemble. Bach 12/11/35, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2485. Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic. 2/27/55; 10/10/54, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2491. Glenn Gould, CBC Centenary Concert, 1967-11-22; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2497. Furtwangler. Wagner. Bayreuth Festival 7/19/36; BPO 4/27/54; BSOO 10/3/47, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2498. Stereo 78 Radio Program, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2499. Tennstedt, LPO. Mahler. Osaka 4/13/84; Mehta, NY Philharmonic. Gershwin. Osaka 8/18/84, 1984; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2500. Karajan, Berlin Philharmonic. Strauss 2/23/85; Tennstedt, London Philharmonic. Mozart. Osaka 4/13/84, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2501. Karajan, Vienna Philharmonic. Tchaikovsky. Szerthburg, 1985-08-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2502. Karajan, Berlin Philharmonic. Brahms 11/24/84; 12/12/84, 1984; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2503. Karajan, Berlin Philharmonic. Strauss, 1984-11-234; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2504. Abbado, Vienna Philharmonic. Beethoven. Tokyo, 1987-03-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2505. Abbado, Vienna Philharmonic. Beethoven. Tokyo, 1987-03-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2506. Abbado, Vienna Philharmonic. Beethoven. Tokyo, 1987-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2507. Abbado, Vienna Philharmonic. Beethoven. Tokyo, 1987-03-25; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2508. Abbado, Vienna Philharmonic. Beethoven. Tokyo, 1987-03-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2509. Stravinsky, NY Philharmonic 3/1/53; Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic 4/19/53; Rubinstein 4/12/53; Kapell, 1987-03-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2510. Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic 4/10/53; 11/15/53; 11/29/53; 4/20/52; Szell 1/11/53; Walter 1/4/53, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2516. Hofmann 1, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2517. Hofmann 2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2533. Unger, CBC Toronto Symphony, Gould. Beethoven, Concerto No.3 in C minor, 1955-02-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2534. Gould, CBC. Gibbons; Bach, 1956-01-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2535. MacMillan, Toronto Symphony, Gould. Beethoven, Concerto No.2. CBC, 1951-12-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2536. Fournet, Concertgebouw. Roussel, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2537. Strauss, Berlin State Opera Orchestra. Beethoven, Symphony No.5 [Brunswick 78s], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2539. Budapest Quartet, Serkin. Library of Congress, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)
- 2540. Adler, Baltimore Symphony, Gould 10/9/62; 1/2/62, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 23)